Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.fourtee Mss.B.B61.inventory14
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents W
  - West Indies National Emergency Committee (Box 95)
    - To Boas
    - Found at end of Dec. 1940
  - Westergaard, H. (Box 95)
    - To Graves, W. W., 1919 Oct. 14; 1p
    - Enc. originally with Graves, W., 1919 Dec. 4; 3p
    - From Graves, W. W., 1919 Sep. 7; 3p
  - Westerhaus, Hermann (Box 95)
    - From Boas, 1930 Jan. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Dec. 14; 1p
  - Westermann (Box 95)
    - From Boas, 1925 Nov. 7; 1p
    - Enc. with Boas, F. (to Warnhuis, A.), 1925 Nov. 7
  - Westermann, B., Co. (Box 95)
    - From Boas, 1925 Mar. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Feb. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Mar. 4; 1p
  - Westermann, D. (Box 95)
    - From Boas, 1927 Oct. 31; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Jan. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 Feb. 13; 2p
    - From Boas, 1930 May 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 June 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1930 June 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 June 6; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Feb. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Aug. 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1925 Sep. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1926 Apr. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Oct. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Nov. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Nov. 19; 2p
    - To Boas, 1930 Jan. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Apr. 7; 2p
    - To Boas, 1930 June 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 June 3; 1p
    - See Boas, F. (to Fackenthal, F.D.), 1931 May 19
    - To Boas, 1931 May 31; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 June 30; 2p
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Mar. 9; 2p
    - To Boas, 1932 May 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 July 12; 1p
  - Westermann, William L. (Box 95)
    - From Boas, 1934 May 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1942 Mar. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 May 4; 1p
  - Westermayr, Arthur (Box 95)
    - To Boas, 1910 May 16
  - Westersheim, Ritter Wettstein (Box 95)
    - From Boas, 1920 May 29; 1p
  - Weston, M. M.II (Box 95)
    - To Boas, 1933 Mar. 30; 1p
  - Wettstein, I. (Box 95)
    - To Boas, 1930 Jan. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 July 23
  - Wettstein, Richard (Box 95)
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Oct. 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1922 Jan. 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Jan. 29; 2p
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 May 4; 2p
    - To Boas, 1921 Aug. 20; 4p
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 10; 8p
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 13; 2p
    - To Boas, 1927 Dec. 28; 3p
    - To Beck, Carl, 1920 Nov. 14; 1p
    - Enc. with Lieber, Hugo, 1920 Dec. 16
  - Weule, Karl (Box 95)
    - From Boas, 1912 Oct. 4
    - From Boas, 1912 Nov. 7
    - From Boas, 1912 Dec. 13
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 21
    - From Boas, 1913 June 16
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 15
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 20
    - From Boas, 1914 Jan. 24
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb. 17
    - From Boas, 1914 Feb. 20
    - To Boas, 1912 July 13; 2p
    - To Boas, 1912 Sep. 5; 2p
    - To Boas, 1912 Dec. 2
    - To Boas, 1913 June 26
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 6
    - To Boas, 1914 Feb. 6
  - Wever, W. (Box 95)
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 23; 2p
    - See Boas, F. (to Francke, K.), 1905 Nov. 28
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1905 Dec. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1905 Dec. 14; 1p
    - From Boas, 1906 Jan. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1906 Feb. 6; 2p
    - From Boas, 1906 Oct. 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1906 Oct. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1906 Nov. 30; 2p
    - From Boas, 1906 Dec. 14; 2p
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 7; 2p
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 24
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 2; 2p
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 16
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 21; 4p
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 30; 3p
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1906 May 17; 1p
    - To Boas, 1906 Sep. 6; 2p
    - To Boas, 1906 Sep. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1906 Oct. 9; 2p
    - To Boas, 1906 Oct. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1906 Oct. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1906 Oct. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1906 Oct. 18; 2p
    - To Boas, 1906 Dec. 4; 1p
  - Weybright, Victor (Box 95)
    - From Boas, 1937 Aug. 3; 1p
  - Weyer, E. M. Jr. (Box 95)
    - From Boas, 1929 Dec. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Dec. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Dec. 12; 2p
  - Weyhe, Ernst (Box 95)
    - To Boas, 1886 Mar. 21
  - Weyland, P. (Box 95)
    - To Boas, 1921 Nov. 29; 3p
  - Weymouth, F. W. (Box 95)
    - From Boas, 1941 Oct. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1942 Mar. 17; 1p
  - Wheeler (Box 95)
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 15
  - Wheeler, B. I. (Box 95)
    - From Kroeber, A.L., 1905 Oct. 31
    - See Kroeber, A.L., 1905 Nov. 1
  - Wheeler, Everett P. (Box 95)
    - From Boas, 1905 Jan. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1905 May 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1904 Dec. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1905 Jan. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1905 Feb. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1905 Mar. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1905 May 9
  - Wheeler, J. H. (Box 95)
    - From Laufer, B., 1905 Jan. 25
  - Wheeler, Joseph L. (Box 95)
    - From Boas, 1929 Dec. 13; 2p
    - To Boas, 1929 Dec. 9; 1p
      Enc. Amer. Ass. for the Advancement of Science
  - Wheeler, J. R. (Box 95)
    - From Boas, 1913 Nov. 25
    - To Boas, 1909 Feb. 3
  - Wheeler, William Morton (Box 95)
    - From Boas, 1917 Feb. 20
    - From Boas, 1917 Oct. 12
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 26; 1p
    - From Boas, 1922 Nov. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 May 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1917 Oct. 15; 2p
    - To Boas, 1933 May 25; 3p
  - Wheelwright, M. (Box 95)
    - From Boas, 1927 July 1; 1p
  - Whelan, Joseph (Box 95)
    - From Boas, 1917 Dec. 15; 2p
    - From Boas, 1918 Jan. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1918 Apr. 15; 6p
    - From Boas, 1918 Apr. 18; 1p
  - Whelpley, A. W. Public Library of Cincinnati (Box 95)
    - To Boas, 1898 Dec. 13; 1p
  - Whelpton, P. K. (Box 95)
    - From Boas, 1937 Oct. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Oct. 5; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Mar. 9; 1p
  - Whicher, George M. (Box 95)
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 25; 2p
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Sep. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 28; 2p
    - To Boas, 1920 Sep. 15; 2p
    - To Boas, 1920 Sep. 25; 4p
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 4; 6p
  - Whipper, Rose L. (Box 95)
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 24
    - From Boas, 1924 Dec. 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1932 Nov. 7; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 May 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1913 Feb. 20
    - To Boas, 1930 Oct. 25; 4p
    - To Boas, 1932 Oct. 20; 5p
    - To Boas, 1932 Nov. 16; 2p
    - To Boas, 1936 May 9; 2p
    - To Boas, 1936 June 6; 3p
  - Whipple, G. H. (Box 95)
    - From Boas, 1931 Jan. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Jan. 26; 1p
  - Whirtil, Max (Box 95)
    - To Boas, 1938 Dec. 5; 1p
  - White (Box 95)
    - From Noyes, W. A., 1931 Mar. 2
    - From Boas, 1906 Mar. 22
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 19
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 12
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 29
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 17
    - To Boas, 1906 Aug. 14
  - White, Amelia E. (Box 95)
    - From Boas, 1924 Jan. 24; 2p
    - From Boas, 1927 Dec. 5; 2p
    - From Boas, 1928 Oct. 17; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 Oct. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Jan. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Dec. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Jan. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Jan. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 Oct. 22; 1p
  - White, Amos J. (Box 95)
    - From Boas, 1907 Apr. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1907 Apr. 18; 2p
  - White, Andrew D. (Box 95)
    - From Boas, 1904 Dec. 21; 2p
    - From Boas, 1905 Nov. 17; 2p
    - From Boas, 1905 Dec. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1905 Dec. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1906 Jan. 2; 4p
    - From Boas, 1908 Nov. 10
    - See letter to Butler, Nicholas Murray, dated Nov. 10, 1908
    - From Boas, 1910 Jan. 21
    - To Boas, 1898 July 18
    - To Boas, 1904 Dec. 23; 2p
    - To Boas, 1905 Jan. 2; 2p
    - To Boas, 1905 Dec. 1; 5p
  - White, Aubrey (Box 95)
    - To Boas, 1888 Jan. 6; 1p
  - White, Bailey (Box 95)
    - To Boas, 1939 Feb. 9; 2p
  - White, David McA. (Box 95)
    - See Boas, F. Open letter on culture and democracy in Spain. Replies, Jan. 1938
  - White, Francis (Box 95)
    - From Boas, 1931 Sep. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Sep. 21; 2p
    - To Abbot, C. G., 1930 June 5; 1p
    - Enc. with Stirling, M. W., 1930 June 9
  - White, Gaylord (Box 95)
    - From Boas, 1908 May 12
    - From Boas, 1908 May 28
    - To Boas, 1908 May 27
  - White, J. W. (Box 95)
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 20; 1p
  - White, John (Box 95)
    - From Boas, 1936 Dec. 3; 1p
  - White, John S. (Box 95)
    - To Boas, 1887 Nov. 10
  - White, John W. (Box 95)
    - To Boas, 1902 Oct. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1902 Nov. 18; 1p
  - White, Joseph J. (Box 95)
    - From Boas, 1939 Apr. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Apr. 3; 2p
    - To Boas, 1939 June 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Sep. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Sep. 28; 2p
    - To Boas, 1939 Oct. 2; 1p
  - White, Katrine N. (Box 95)
    - From Boas, 1934 Oct. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Oct. 4; 1p
  - White, Dr. Leonard D. (Box 95)
    - From Boas, 1930 Jan. 13; 1p
    - To Boas
    - See Tufts, H. H., 1929 Dec. 17
    - To Boas, 1929 Dec. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Jan. 9; 1p
  - White, Dr. Leslie (Box 95)
    - From Boas, 1931 Sep. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1936 Apr. 16; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Sep. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1935 July 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 8; 1p
  - White, Newman I. (Box 95)
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 27
    - From Boas, 1920 Mar. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Feb. 28; 2p
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 12; 2p
    - To Boas, 1920 June 12; 1p
  - White, Samuel S. (Box 95)
    - From Boas, 1924 Dec. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Nov. 30; 1p
  - White, Trumbull (Box 95)
    - From Boas, 1914 Oct. 5
    - From Boas, 1914 Nov. 10
    - To Boas, 1914 Oct. 1; 2p
    - To Boas, 1914 Oct. 6
    - To Boas, 1931 May 3; 1p
  - White, W. A. (Box 95)
    - Found at end of Dec. 1939
  - White, W. L. (Box 95)
    - To Boas, 1939 Mar. 10; 1p
  - White, Walter (Box 95)
    - From Boas, 1936 Oct. 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Sep. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1942 May 25; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 Mar. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Mar. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Apr. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Sep. 24; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Oct. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Oct. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Sep. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Dec. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1942 May 27; 1p
  - S. S. White Dental Mfg. Co. (Box 95)
    See Dental Cosmos
  - White Sands News (se desgaidoh hani) (Box 95)
    - See Reichard, G. A., 1934 July 29
  - Whitehead, George G. (Box 95)
    - To Boas, 1926 Nov. 1; 1p
  - Whitehouse Conference (Box 95)
    - Blackfan, Kenneth D., 2/12/30, 2/14/30, 2/18/30, 3/28/30, 5/13/30, 5/27/30, 6/4/30, 6/18/30
    - Davis, Hallowell, 1/19/31, 2/2/31
    - Franzen, Raymond, 4/7/30, 3/28/30
    - Stuart, Harold C., 3/20/30, 3/24/30, 6/23/30
  - Whitener, H. C. (Box 95)
    - From Boas, 1931 May 19; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 June 1; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 June 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 May 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 June 6; 1p
  - Whiting, G. (Box 95)
    - From Boas, 1923 Feb. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Feb. 19; 2p
  - Whitman, George (Box 95)
    - History of the United Students Peace Committee
    - Enc. with Gordon, Sylvia, 1940 Mar. 28; 1p
  - Whitney, Annie Weston (Box 95)
    - To Boas, 1896 Dec. 21
  - Whitney, E. (Box 95)
    - To Boas, 1935 Mar. 28; 1p
  - Whitney, Florence (Mrs. Caspar) (Box 95)
    - From Boas, 1940 Jan. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Jan. 22; 1p
  - Whitney, L. F. (Box 95)
    - To Boas, 1926 May 22; 1p
  - Whitney, Marian P. (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1906 Jan. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1906 Mar. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1905 Jan. 8; 4p
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 10; 3p
    - To Boas, 1906 Jan. 22; 3p
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 25; 2p
    - To Boas, 1906 Mar. 18; 2p
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 1; 2p
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 2; 4p
    - To Boas, 1906 Apr. 4; 2p
  - Whitney, Mary W. (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1906 Nov. 30; 2p
  - Whorf, B. L. (Benjamin) (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1931 Sep. 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Jan. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 May 3; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Nov. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Nov. 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Jan. 20; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Oct. 19; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Oct. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Sep. 28; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Feb. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Feb. 19; 5p
    - To Boas, 1937 Apr. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Aug. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Nov. 19; 3p
    - To Boas, 1937 Nov. 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Jan. 21; 2p
    - To Boas, 1939 Oct. 23; 1p
    - To Tozzer, A. M., 1930 Oct. 1; 1p
  - Who's Who in America Editor (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1917 June 4
  - Whymant, N. (Box 96)
    - To Boas, 1926 May 7; 1p
    - Enc: Fewkes, J. W. (to Whymant, N), 1926 May 5
    - From Fewkes, J. W., 1926 May 5
    - Enc: with Whymant, N., 1926 May 7
  - Whyre, John (Box 96)
    - See Boas, F. Open letter on culture and democracy in Spain. Replies., 1938 Jan.
  - Wiberg, Allan (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 11
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 9; 2p
  - Wichmann, Hugo (Box 96)
    - To Boas, 1886 May 31
    - To Boas, 1890 Feb. 19
  - Wickersham, James (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1907 Aug. 9; 2p
    - To Boas, 1907 June 28; 3p
  - Wickman, E. K. (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1930 Nov. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1930 Nov. 13; 1p
  - Wicks, Stanton D. (Box 96)
    - To Boas, 1936 Apr. 7; 1p
  - Wieding, J. (Box 96)
    - To Boas, 1914 May 11
  - Wiehl, Dorothy (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1930 Oct. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 24; 1p
  - Wien - Akademischer Senat der Universitat (Box 96)
    See Dopsch
  - Wien - Akademie der Wissenschaften in Wien (Box 96)
    See Radermacher, Ludwig
  - Wien - Bibliothek der Gesellschaft der Arzte (Box 96)
    - To Boas, 1920 Feb. 28; 6p
  - Wien - Bundesamt für Statistik Wien, Austria (Box 96)
    See Schiff
  - Wien - Kartographisches Institut (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1923 May 8; 2p
    - From Boas, 1926 Jan. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 June 11; 1p
  - Wien - K.K. Naturhistorisches Hofmuseum - Anthropologisch Ethnographisches Abtcilung (Box 96)
    - 1907 Aug. 1, 2p
  - Wien - Kartographisches, früher Militargeographisches Institut in Wien (Box 96)
    - To Boas, 1923 Jan. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1923 June 9; 2p
    - To Boas, 1923 June 18; 2p
  - Wiener, Arthur (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1913 Nov. 1
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 29
  - Wiener, Felix F. (Box 96)
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 19; 1p
  - Wiener, Philip Paul (Box 96)
    - To Boas, 1938 Nov. 30; 1p
      Enc: Aims and scope of a proposed Journal of the history of ideas.
  - Wierum, Otto C. (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1911 June 9
    - From Boas, 1911 June 12
    - From Boas, 1939 July 1; 1p
    - To Boas, 1911 June 10; 2p
    - To Boas, 1911 June 14
    - To Boas, 1939 May 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 July 7; 1p
  - Wiesbaden - Nassauischer Verein für Naturkunde Wiesbaden, Germany (Box 96)
    - To Boas, 1923 Mar. 6; 1p
  - Wieschhoff, Heinz (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1936 Feb. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1937 Sep. 30; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Jan. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1938 Apr. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 July 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Sep. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Sep. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Nov. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1937 Sep. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Jan. 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Jan. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1938 Mar. 7; 2p
  - Wiese, L. von (Box 96)
    - See TC6nnies, 1924 Apr.
    - Found at end of Apr. 1924
    - To Boas, 1926 Nov. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Jan. 2; 1p
  - Wiesenberg, Alex (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 2; 1p
  - Wiggam, A. E. (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 5
  - Wigmore, John H. (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1916 Feb. 23
  - Wilbur, C. M. (Box 96)
    - To Boas, 1939 July 18; 1p
  - Wilbur, Lillian Fredericks (Box 96)
    - See Wilbur, Walter K., 1940 Nov. 12
  - Wilbur, Ray Lyman (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1933 Feb. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1932 Oct. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1933 Feb. 24; 1p
  - Wilbur, Walter K. (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1940 Feb. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 Mar. 8; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 Nov. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1940 Dec. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Feb. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Mar. 20; 1p
    - To Boas Enc., 1940 Nov. 12; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec. 8; 1p
  - Wilder, H. H. (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 1; 1p
  - Wildman, Edwin (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Aug. 18; 1p
  - Wildner, B. G. (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1909 May 14
    - To Boas, 1909 May 11
  - Wile, Ira S. (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1934 Jan. 30; 1p
    - To Boas, 1918 Jan. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1934 Jan. 29; 1p
  - Wilhelm, Roy C. (Box 96)
    - To Boas, 1924 Mar. 31; 1p
  - Wilkinson, Hubert (Box 96)
    - To Boas, 1941 Nov. 1; 1p
  - Wilkinson, M. (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 20
    - From Boas, 1917 May 3
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 19
  - Will, George F. (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 27
    - To Boas, 1912 Jan. 20
    - To Boas, 1912 Jan. 30
    - To Boas, 1913 Feb. 2
  - Will, G. K. (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1933 July 11; 2p
  - Willard (Box 96)
    - To Boas, 1904 Feb. 19
  - Willcox, W. F. (Box 96)
    - To Boas, 1910 May 31; 2p
  - Wille, Jakob (Box 96)
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 9; 1p
      Enc. List of Publications
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 22; 1p
  - Williams (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1905 Jan. 25
    - To Boas, 1905 Feb. 8
    - From Boas, 1912 Oct. 22
  - Williams, C. C. -- (see Williamson) (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1942 Oct. 12; 1p
  - Williams, Charles, M. (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1924 Feb. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1924 Feb. 6; 2p
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 10
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 20
  - Williams, Frances M. (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1939 Apr. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 Apr. 11; 1p
    - To Boas, 1939 May 12; 1p
  - Williams, Frankwood E. (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 14; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 11; 2p
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 30; 2p
    - Enc. International congress on mental hygiene, 1936 July 16; 1p
  - Williams, Frederick R. (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1934 Apr. 10; 1p
  - Williams, George Dee (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1936 Feb. 3; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 25; 1p
    - Found at end of Dec. 1936
  - Williams, H. B. (Box 96)
    - To Miller, C. R., 1939 July 7; 1p
  - Williams, Hadwen Harry (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1919 Dec. 11; 1p
    - To Journal of Amer. Folk Lore, 1919 Oct. 26; 1p
  - Williams, H. S. (Box 96)
    - To Boas, 1912 Oct. 10
  - Williams, Jesse Feiring (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1940 Jan. 22; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 Jan. 17; 1p
  - Williams, L. R. (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 10; 1p
  - Williams, R. H. (Box 96)
    - See Boas, F., 1905 Jan. 24
    - See Boas, F., 1905 Jan. 30
    - To Boas, 1908 Dec. 15
    - From Laufer, B., 1905 Jan. 30
  - Williams, S. P. (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1927 Nov. 9; 2p
  - Williams, W. B. (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 10; 1p
    - To Boas, 1929 Oct. 9; 1p
  - Williams & Wilkins Co. (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 4; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 31; 1p
    - From Boas, 1923 Oct. 27; 1p
    - From Boas, 1926 Nov. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1901 Oct. 31; 2p
    - To Boas, 1923 Oct. 30; 1p
      See Thomas, Charles C.
  - Williamson, C. C. (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1942 Nov. 23; 1p
    - To Boas, 1942 Dec. 10; 1p
    - From Boas, 1942 Oct. 12; 1p
  - Williamson & Smith (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1907 Sep. 11
    - To Boas, 1907 Aug. 20; 2p
    - To Boas, 1907 Sep. 5
    - To Boas, 1907 Sep. 26; 2p
  - Willis, Bailey (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1939 Feb. 16; 1p
  - Willman, Stephen M. (Box 96)
    - To Dept. of Justice (U.S.), 1917 Nov. 1
  - Willmore, Elliot G. (Box 96)
    - To Boas, 1917 Mar. 13
  - Willner, Alan (Box 96)
    - To Boas, 1940 Nov. 4; 1p
  - Willner, Alan and Stone, P. (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1940 Nov. 7; 1p
  - Willoughby (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1907 Mar. 23
    - From Boas, 1907 Mar. 27
  - Willoughby, Charles C. (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1921 Nov. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Dec. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1894 May 8; 1p
  - Willoughby, Charles C. (cont'd) (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1907 Mar. 23
    - From Boas, 1907 Mar. 27
    - From Boas, 1921 Nov. 23; 1p
    - From Boas, 1921 Dec. 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1894 May 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1907 Mar. 26
    - To Boas, 1907 Nov. 1
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 26
    - To Boas, 1921 Nov. 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 Nov. 26; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 Dec. 29; 1p
  - Willoughby's (Box 96)
    - To Boas, 1933 Apr. 23
    - To Boas, 1933 May 4
    - To Boas, 1933 May 5
    - To Boas, 1934 Apr. 10
    - To Boas, 1934 Apr. 23
    - To Boas, 1934 May 4
    - To Boas, 1934 May 5
    - To Boas, 1934 Sep. 15
  - Wilson, Charles Bundy (Box 96)
    - 1906 Feb. 20, 1p
    - 1906 Mar. 18, 1p
    - 1908 May 26
    - 1908 June 8
    - 1909 Mar. 27
    - 1911 Aug. 22
    - 1914 Oct. 16
    - 1914 Nov. 19
  - Wilson, Sir Daniel (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1891 Feb. 20
    - From Boas, 1891 May 12
    - To Boas, 1889 July 9; 2p
    - To Boas, 1889 July 12; 3p
    - To Boas, 1889 Oct. 22
    - To Boas, 1890 May 23
    - To Boas, 1891 Feb. 18
    - To Boas, 1891 Mar. 16
    - To Boas, 1891 Mar. 21
    - To Boas, 1891 May 25
    - To Boas, 1891 June 3
    - To Boas, 1891 Nov. 16; 3p
  - Wilson, Edmond B. (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1939 Jan. 17
      See Boas, F. (to Butler, N.M.)
    - To Boas, 1939 Jan. 3; 1p
  - Wilson, Edward F. (Box 96)
    - To Boas, 1888 Apr. 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1889 Nov. 8
    - To Boas, 1889 Nov. 21
    - To Boas, 1889 Dec. 26
  - Wilson, Edwin B. (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1914 Nov. 27
    - From Boas, 1917 Feb. 20
    - From Boas, 1927 Mar. 22; 1p
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 May 11; 1p
    - From Boas, 1928 May 18; 2p
    - From Boas, 1928 Nov. 24; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 29; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Nov. 12; 1p
    - From Boas, 1939 Jan. 18; 1p
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1928 May 15; 2p
    - See Cole, F. C., 1930 Feb. 19
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Dec. 5; 1p
  - Wilson, Elliott H. (Box 96)
    - See Haury, E. W., 1927 Mar. 2
  - Wilson, E. M. B. (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1921 Sep. 7; 1p
    - To Boas, 1921 Aug. 12; 1p
  - Wilson, E. R. and Lowenberg, E. (Box 96)
    - To Boas, 1930 Mar. 3; 32p
  - Wilson, G. R. (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1931 Jan. 28; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 16; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 Apr. 9; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 June 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1931 June 29; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Jan, 21; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 6; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 Apr. 8; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 May 27; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 June 4; 1p
    - To Boas, 1931 June 9; 1p
  - Wilson, Harry L. (Box 96)
    - To Boas, 1910 Jan. 12
    - To Boas, 1910 Jan. 21
    - To Boas, 1911 Jan. 16
    - To Boas, 1911 Feb. 5
  - Wilson, H. R. (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1931 June 2; 1p
    - To Boas, 1912 Feb. 8
    - To Boas, 1937 Sep. 8; 2p
    - To Boas, 1937 Sep. 10; 1p
  - Wilson, H. W. Co. (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr, 5; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 15; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 18; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 2; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 13; 1p
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 13; 1p
    - per J. M. Rowell, 1920 Apr. 13; 1p
    - To Boas, 1920 Sep. 13; 1p
      See Rowell, W. C.
  - Wilson, Huntington (Box 96)
    - To Boas, 1911 Aug. 30
  - Wilson, J. (Box 96)
    - To Boas, 1942 Nov. 26; 1p
  - Wilson, James Grant (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1899 Dec. 14; 2p
    - From Boas, 1908 May 25
    - From Boas, 1908 June 9
    - To Boas, 1899 Dec. 15; 1p
    - To Boas, 1908 June 10
  - Wilson, J. S. (Box 96)
    - To Boas, 1887 Dec. 23
  - Wilson, Louis N. (Box 96)
    - From Boas, 1914 Oct. 21; 2p
    - From Boas, 1914 Oct. 23